Register of the UFA motion picture newsreels
Hoover Institution Archives
- Motion Picture Films, 1939-1945 (Film shelf)
  - UFA, Inland, 1939-1945
    - Reel 569
      1. Eastern Front, Goering, General Student greet officers of Crete attack; 2. Goering meets with Croatian Vice President; 3. Denmark, Danish volunteers march through city; 4. Spain, Blue Division leaves on train; 5. Italy, Prince Umberto waves goodbye to troops; 6. Germany, Red Cross people in station; 7. Map of Kirkenes, German destroyers on Mirmansk coast; 8. German and Finnish troops advancing; 9. Map of Europe, infantry advancing through woods, some Russians surrender; 10. Dniester River, infantry cross river; 11. Russian prisoners; 12. Ukraine, youth volunteer for German army; 13. Hungarian cavalry advances; 14. Troops crossing temporary bridge; 15. Slovakian and German troops advance; 16. Map of Kiev, Dnieper River, troops cross river; 17. Map of Polotsk, troops advance into city, street fighting; 18. Don River, engineers build bridge; 19. Troops encounter Russian resistance, Russians surrender.
      20. Cavalry advance, scorched earth tactics; 21. Infantry advances; 22. Prisoners march back; 23. Vyazma, infantry advances toward town; 24. Map of Baltic states, bombing of railroad; 25. Bodies of dead piled together; 26. SS troops advancing in field; 27. Two prisoners, one wounded; 28. Prisoners sitting; 29. Russian fortifications on fire; 30. Artillery fire on town; 31. Several soldiers and one prisoner; 32. German tank goes past prisoners; 33. Infantry, tanks advance past burning houses; 34. German planes on first bombing of Moscow.
    - Reel 570
      1. Eastern Front, Hitler visits front, meets with officers; 2. Dutch volunteers and families leave on train; 3. Croatia, Croatian troops and civilians volunteer; 4. Italy, Italian trucks leave for Eastern Front; 5. Map of Northern Front, Salla, artillery firing; 6. Map of front line, Romanian and German officers meet; 7. German troops cross river under fire; 8. Russian prisoners; 9. More murdered people, Jews pushed toward camp; 10. Map of Vinnytsa, civilians repair streets, Hungarian troops advancing with tanks; 11. Map of Mogilev and Smolensk, heavy artillery fire; 12. Wrecks of Russian planes; 13. War booty collected; 14. Many Russian prisoners; 15. Infantry advancing, heavy street fighting, take Smolensk.
      20. Infantry column marches; 21. German bombers on run over Moscow; 22. Abandoned Russian munitions train; 23. German troops repair telephone wires; 24. Waffen SS, artillery fire; 25. Russians surrender; 26. Repairing streets and bridges; 27. Troops advancing; 28. Russians with white flags; 29. German troops enter burning village; 30. Soldiers tear down barricade; 31. Artillery on Russian positions; 32. Russian planes attack; 33. German fighters take off after Russian planes.
  - UFA, Ausland, 1939-1945
    The Ausland film versions of the collection were intended for a specific foreign audience. These reels are primarily in Spanish and include 16mm and 35mm films. These versions differ from their Inland counterparts.
    The followings reels have not yet been described: 519-521, 523-547, 549-550, 555, 557-560, 562-581, 583-588, 590, 597.
  - 135 unidentified reels
- Photographs
  - 130 photos of German military forces on maneuvers, in military parades, and during invasions of the low countries, France, North Africa, and Russia, 1940 (Envelope A-B)
    Includes photos of munitions factory workers.
  - 21 photos of Nazi leaders (including Hitler, Hess, Goering, Goebbels, Donetz, and Rader), as well as photos of Mussolini, undated (Envelope C)